

Bogatinovska

Software Engineer

Contact



+38972207429



bogatinovska.ana@gmail.com



https://github.com/AnaBogatinovska



www.linkedin.com/in/ana-bogatinovska



Ana's Personal Portfolio & Resume

Skills

- JavaScript, Typescript
- Dart, Flutter
- Angular 13+
- Vue.js
- AWS Amplify Auth
- RxJs, NgRx, Vuex
- YouTrack, Trello
- GitHub
- LocalStorage

Education

High School 'Pance Arsovski'- Skopje, North Macedonia

> September 2008- June 2012 Skopje

Online course for Frontend Web Developer-Skopje, North Macedonia

> October 2020- December 2020 FINKI- Skopie

About Me

I am a dedicated Software Engineer with solid experience in building user-friendly, responsive web and mobile interfaces. My technical expertise includes JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, Dart, and Flutter, among other modern frameworks. I excel at problem-solving, tackling challenges with enthusiasm, and ensuring effective communication within diverse teams. My goal is to drive digital projects that make a significant, positive impact.

Experience

MFactor Consultancy - Melbourne, Australia

Software Engineer

12.2021 - present (Remote)

- Developed user-friendly responsive web & mobile interfaces
- Code reviews, identify bugs, implement necessary fixes and improvements
- Close communication with backend developers
- Skills: JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular 13+, Angular Material, Tailwind, Fuse Angular, Flutter, Ionic Framework, GitHub, YouTrack, Trello, Vue 2, RxJs, NgRx Store, Vuex Store

Musala Soft - Skopje, North Macedonia

Junior Software Engineer

04.2021 - 11.2021

- Worked on company internal web application
- Involved in a project for developing FloorPlan
- Skills: JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular 12+, Vue 2, RxJs, NgRx Store. Vuex Store

FX3X - Skopje, North Macedonia

Vfx Roto Artist

08 2015 - 05 2020

- Roto animation of movie footage from a given deadline
- Proficiency in team work
- Successful completion of the work within a given deadline

Projects

- **Annadaan Ammucare** Food donations for people or animals across India. Front end technologies: JavaScript, Typescript, Angular/Ionic Framework
 - Web: annadaan.ammucare
 - Google Play Store: annadaan.ammucare
 - App Store: annadaan.ammucare
- Act4Hunger Food Donation ACT 4 Hunger (A4H) is a global charitable platform that serves food to the hungry. Front end technologies: Flutter(Dart), Riverpod
 - Google Play Store: act4hunger
 - App Store: act4hunger
- Reztor Restorations This project provides a powerful tool for managing jobs, assigning tasks, generating quotes and invoices, and to create perfect communication between team members. Front end technologies: Angular, Fuse Template, Tailwind CSS
- Medtech Pulz Web project which is an Admin portal where doctors can login and review a patient's heart health history and download or preview raw ECG data for further processing and analysis.